[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "By the way, why are you in so much debt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "The bottom line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Whatever came afterwards, whatever context he was trying to put it in, it sounded bad, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "It sounded bad and it all sounded I hate to say very naive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CFP"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Do you think they have gotten away with it in many ways?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "I think many bankers have got away with it, but I think many of the executives on wall street have got away with it as well which is why the CFP, the consumer financial protection bureau that President Obama put into place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Do you think America is now coming out of the recession?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "So, why get them back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I mean, to me, it's very worrying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "This is serious stuff, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It's serious but it's been serious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "The country as a business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Well, the country as a business isn't running like a good business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Do you think, as many do, that America needs to go back to building things rather than consuming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I think they do need to go back to building things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Why is it the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "It's the way because it got so expensive to hire a laborer here with the insurance, with everything, we couldn't afford it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "They should be looking after their own country, shouldn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "But, in their way, they are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "When you graduate college, if you had 20, 30, $40,000 as student loan debt, how would that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "$", "CD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "It would make me feel awful.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$40,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Suze, what do you do then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "He should go to the college that gives him 100 percent scholarship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Suze, the problem is not specific comparison, people will get a better education at a private school right now than they would from a non-thief main school in America, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "They would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Got it people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "That's a good answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What kind of advice would you give them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "They are nervous about that kind of commitment because they don't have 20 percent down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "That's gone, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "That's gone for now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Isn't that a better way of looking at this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "That has change, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Are you ready for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Did you just say helping your siblings with a wedding is more of a priority for you over getting out of credit card debt or saving money for your own retirement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "It's not more of a priority, but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Do I have to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["15 percent"]}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "At what interest rate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "If I average everything out, it's probably around like 15 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What were they doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Shopping.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "It's like you have to be personally responsible, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "There's a saying that I have, when you feel less than, you spend more than.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Given all the attacks that have come on you, is there anything you will change about the card?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Yes, there will be one thing I change about the card.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Well, I was trying, deny, deny, deny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "We should be saluting him, shouldn't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I think we should be saluting him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Natalie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Hi Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "What is our problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "RMAN: You live in New York City.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What are things that most people are wasteful about, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Almost everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What are the most common ways people waste money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Well, I personally would tell you weddings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Isn't it worse to do that than stay at home and make love with each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "-- too much of my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "But do you feel at times like your spirit is broken, because nobody is listening to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I want to rally the troops, you see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "About 3,000?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Oh, how did I know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "That was really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Now, so how much credit card dent do you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I was afraid you were going to ask me that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Fifteen, 20?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "About that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Did I impress you again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "This is now getting very, very unusual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "If I could relive a moment for you, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "You know, I have had so many.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "The luckiest thing that has ever happened to me, the greatest thing that has happened to me is KT.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Because all the money in the world, actually, if you don't have love in your life, is pointless, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "So that's the greatest thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "The other signature question of mine, of course, is how many times, Suze, have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "One.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "GOP pick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]